http://www.nicenstripy.com/privacy-policy

This website uses Cookies for an enhanced user experience, social media sharing and Google analytics. We do not store any personal information. To read our cookies policy in full please click here.
If you would like to change your cookie settings at any time, please see http://www.aboutcookies.org for more information on how to change your cookie settings or block cookies altogether.
This website uses cookies, to read our cookies policy in full please click here.
Accept & hide message
Yes - Got It, hide message
Login / Register     Become a Franchise
0800 014 2420
Home
About
What our customers say
Our credentials
Privacy Policy
We ask that you read this privacy policy carefully as it contains important information about what to expect when nicenstripy collects personal information about you and how nicenstripy will use your personal data. This policy applies to information we collect about: visitors to our website, people who do business with us and people who register for our newsletter and other updates.
1. The information we collect about you
We may collect personal information from you. Personal information may include your name, postal address, email address, telephone number and date of birth amongst other things. Most of the personal information we collect will be provided by you. Occasionally we may receive information about you from other sources (such as your bank, employer and credit reference agencies) which we will add to the information which we already hold about you in order to help us provide legal services.
2. How we will use the information about you
We gather this information to allow us to provide the services requested and to carry out marketing of other products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. The relevant information is then used by us to communicate with you on any matter relating to the conduct of your instructions in general. We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us to develop our website and our services. We may also provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify you.
3. Marketing
We may wish to provide you with information about nicenstripy, its employees and/ or any other service we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please send an email message to info@nicenstripy.co.uk stating ‘please do not send me any marketing material’. If you agree to us providing you with marketing information, you can always opt out at a later date.
4. Cookies and other information-gathering technologies
4.1 Our website uses cookies. Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of the website which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.
4.2 For more information on which cookies we use and how we use them, see our Cookies policy.
5. How we protect your information
We will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information such as firewalls, browser certification technology, encryption, limited access, use of passwords, etc as appropriate. However, you should be aware that the use of the Internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal information which is transferred from you or to you via the Internet.
6. Access to your information and updating and correcting your information
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please send an email to info@nicenstripy.co.uk or send a letter to us at our registered office. We may make a small charge for this service. We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. If any of the information that you have provided to nicenstripy changes, for example if you change your email address or name, please let us know the correct details by sending an email to your usual contact, or if you do not have a usual contact info@nicenstripy.co.uk. You may ask us, or we may ask you, to correct information you or we think is inaccurate, and you may also ask us to remove information which is inaccurate.
7. Your consent
By submitting your personal information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy.
8 Changes to privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. This privacy policy was last updated on 1 January 2018 to comply with the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR).
9. Links to other websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy applies only to this website so when you access links to other websites you should read their own privacy policies
What our clients say...
"We wouldn't hesitate to recommend them for grass cutting"
An unexpected storm brought down four of our garden fence panels, and having three small children and a garden that backs onto an alleyway, it was important for us to get it fixed quickly. Nicenstripy came out swiftly and fitted our new fence, and even quoted for a lawn treatment while they were there. We wouldn't hesitate to recommend them.
"The garden maintenance team at nicenstripy deliver exactly what we want"
We've used nicenstripy for loads of small jobs over the years, from small-scale lawn care solutions in our front garden to bigger projects like a long overdue clear out in the back garden. Every time our expectations are smashed, and the team at nicenstripy deliver exactly what we want.
"I would definitely recommend them for all grass cutting"
I have found nicenstripy to be extremely professional. They turn up for grass cutting when they say they will and my lawn has never looked better! We tried other grass cutting services and none were as good as the guys at nicenstripy! I would definitely recommend them for all grass cutting and garden maintenance.
"They do all my garden maintenance"
The most important thing I look for from my garden maintenance company is quality and reliability. I cannot fault nicenstripy. Since they have been cutting and treating my lawn, it has never looked better. In fact now they do all my garden maintenance and it has taken all the stress out of gardening. I can potter around doing the fun jobs, leaving nicenstripy to make sure the garden is well maintained!
"They were punctual, friendly and got on with the lawn care well"
Darren and his colleague transformed our scrappy, lumpy back garden into a beautiful lawn! They were punctual, friendly and got on with the job well. They put in a play bark pit around our climbing frame and accommodated my last-minute request for a raised bed for a veggie patch without a problem. They worked hard - especially as access to our garden limited the delivery of topsoil - so a lot of wheelbarrowing was necessary. Darren was also happy to do extras make sure the job was done properly (re-attaching the slide, fixing the garden gate (see my review of fencing in May)
"Would use again for repairing fencing and recommend to friends"
Responded promptly to a request for a quote which was reasonably priced. Arrived on time, removed the old broken fence. New fence installed with quality materials. All old materials removed from site, left clean and tidy. Would use again and recommend to friends. A job very well done, thank you.
"I would definitely recommend them for garden maintenance"
The work was done efficiently and in good time. Paul was friendly and the work was very well done and all the rubbish was removed. And Paul gave advice on maintaining the hedges. I would definitely recommend them to anyone and will use them again. Thank you.
"They also can do odd jobs such as gutter clearing and power washing"
Paul and his crew have been taking care of our weekly lawn maintenance for over two years now. The guys are all hardworking, polite and take huge pride in their work. Best of all, it shows. They also can do odd jobs such as gutter clearing and power washing.
"Honest, reliable, garden maintenance, an extremely nice family firm"
Mr Burchett was able to provide a very competitive estimate for clearing a community garden and boundary hedges. He arrived on the specified date and carried out all the works quoted for and cleared up afterwards. He and his colleagues are quiet and hardworking.
I would recommend Nicenstripy to anyone.
"Winter garden tidy up"
Each year we ask nicenstripy to do an annual tidy up and each year they do an excellent job. I would definitely recommend them.
"Grass and hedge cutting"
We use nicenstripy all throughout the spring/summer months for grass cutting and hedge trimming, they are always happy to take on extra tasks at short notice. Very good work - Very reliable. I would highly recommend them.
05 October 20
Patchy Lawns
01 March 19
When should I start cutting my lawn?
14 May 18
Warning - Birds Nesting!
11 May 18
When should I cut my hedges?
03 May 18
Who are the best value for money gardeners?
Want to work for yourself and benefit from the security of a national organisation? Apply here.
Alternatively enter your details below followed by your enquiry and one of our team will get back to you.
Comments*
Where did you hear about us:
